If it ever was, it was cuz of the
crooked, violent guards, not from any of
the prisoners. So, you get out and
you're a normal, healthy person or No, I
you know, this is the thing about being
released from prison. You think you can
step back into your life again, and you
can't. Your life is never going to be
the same. Because?
Because you're not the same.
You know, everybody comes out of prison
with PTSD, everybody. I can't tell you
how many times I woke up in the middle
of the night
having the same dream that it's count
time and I find myself outside the
prison and I have to figure out how to
get back in to be in my bunk in time for
count time or they're going to send me
to solitary. And I can't figure out how
to get back inside.
I dreamed for 2 years after I got out.
But then, you know, it wears off and
you start thinking about
patching together a career and my
marriage didn't survive it, but um
Sorry. Yeah, yeah, me too. Thank you.
But uh
Who are you to Who are you today?
You know, I I like who I am.
I'm I'm not perfect. Um I can be a an
judgmental
Um
but on this one issue,
I was right and they were wrong. Is the
Trump team better on torture and these
kinds of issues?
They are in an odd way. Trump sometimes
makes the wrong statements.
I'm going to bring back waterboarding
and a hell of a lot worse. No, you're
not. You're talking tough, but no, he
never did any of that stuff. He made
a mistake twice in his first term
appointing very, very bad people as CIA
director. Very bad. Like
uh
Mike Pompeo. Oh my god. The only person
less popular than Mike Pompeo at the CIA
was Mrs. Mike Pompeo. Let me tell you. I
got that from one of his bodyguards.
And then Gina Haspel
>> why? Why?
You,
go get my my dry cleaning. You,
go walk my dog. They're like, "Lady, we
don't work for you. We're protecting
your husband. We're not going to go get
your dry cleaning and walk your dog."
Um the other one was bloody Gina Haspel.
We called her bloody Gina for a good
reason. She flew out to the secret site
to sit in on one of the torture sessions
just because she could.
Just to sit there and enjoy it and take
it all in.
What kind of sick person does something
like that?
>> So so what does that say to you and and
and how do you communicate that to your
son if you're only going to have one
last conversation with him? What are you
going to say to him if this is true?
>> There's a There's a saying in ancient
Greek um that translates to know
thyself.
Right? You really have to trust
yourself. Of course, we all make
mistakes, very big mistakes.
I have, certainly. But you have to trust
your gut.
Like listen, deep down, we all know
the difference between right and wrong,
all of us.
The hard part is actually implementing
the right
when it's not
expedient.
Hey Bev.
So I wanted to follow up on Vegas. When
are you thinking about that for the
trip? What days? So I'm thinking either
the 20th or the 21st. Does that work for
you? I think it does as long as it's
early enough in the month. I think that
probably works.
>> Wait one second. Um
do you mind giving me that Dose, please?
Wait, what did you just say? It's this
really wonderful um supplement for
cholesterol called Dose. Have you seen
it?
This is so crazy. I feel like I'm
literally, Bev, seeing this everywhere.
It is wild.
>> taking it because a friend told me. It
actually tastes like mango and a little
bit of spicy cuz it has turmeric. It
helps your cholesterol. Okay. All right.
Well, I obviously need to do that. That
damn dose is everywhere.
Hey, man. Hey, man. How you doing? Good.
Good. How you been? I've been doing
great, man. Is that you?
Oh, that's us.
Oh, wow.
Are you using that? Yes. Man, everybody
is, man.
It is crazy. I I had not heard about it
until a couple months ago, and now I
feel like everybody's using it. Damn, I
might need to start trying it. Oh, we
do. Yeah. I like that.
>> You want one? You have it here? Man,
stop, man. I got just what you need.
>> Okay. All right. Oh, you got the little
fancy things, huh?
>> go. Okay. All right. Okay, little shot
of something. Mhm. Okay. You Can I
actually have this?
Man, come on, man. All right. Okay. All
right. You only have to tell me once.
>> What's up? Step back, and I'll watch
out.
You sure this is good for me?
>> Oh, it's good. Okay. All right. It'll be
good to you.
Tastes a little like
>> Mango. Okay. But with a little bite.
Okay. It's like this has some pepper in
this. I think.
>> Ain't nothing like getting bit.
What made you start on
start on this?
Man, I'm I'm 60 I'm getting ready to be
65 years old on Monday. Happy birthday
early.
>> That's right. So, this is You think this
is giving you a little something? Oh,
man. It's going to be a part of my life
for a long time. Yeah, man. What what
you want, man? Uh same thing. Same
thing. Same thing. Make me beautiful.
Well,
Bob Kennedy told me a story that just
sticks right here in the front of my
head. He said on November 22nd, 1963,
that terrible day, his mother picked him
up from school early. He was in sixth or
seventh grade. She picked him up from
school early and brought him back home.
They lived in McLean, Virginia at um
a house that they called Hickory Hill.
So,
the Kennedys were very, very close to uh
the CIA director
and his wife,
John McCone.
And Mrs. McCone had died of breast
cancer 6 months earlier. And the
Kennedys were worried about Director
McCone. They were worried that he was
going to harm harm himself.
And so they invited him to dinner every
single night, 7 days a week. And after
dinner, he and Bobby Kennedy Sr. would
go for a swim.
So, when Bob Jr. and his mom get to the
house, he said he got out of the car,
his dad and Director McCone were
standing in the driveway. And when he
walked past them,
he heard his father say,
"Tell me your people didn't do this."
And McCone said, "I don't know who did
it."
He didn't say, "Of course my people
didn't do it."
He said, "I don't know who did it."
And I think that what with what we know
now,
I think it's safe to assume that there
were elements of the CIA. It was not an
official formal CIA policy, you know, XV
kill the president.
I think that there there were elements
of the CIA
uh
that were probably involved. And I'll
add one other thing. When I was
stationed in Pakistan,
the oldest of the old-timers that I
worked with
was this legendary officer. To tell you
the truth, when I got there, I didn't
get his last name. So, I only called him
Jean. Hi, John, this is Jean. Jean, this
is John. I said, "Hi, Jean, nice to nice
to know you. Good to work with you."
And I was there for weeks until somebody
said, I asked a question and somebody
said, "Ask Gately." I said, "Who's
Gately?" "Jean."
I said, "Jean is Jean Gately?"
He said, "Yeah, who'd you think he was?"
I said, "The commander of the Bay of
Pigs operation
is working for me."
And he said, "Yeah."
So, we all lived in the same guest
house. It was a very small guest house.
So, we would have breakfast together, go
to the office, have dinner together.
So, I went up to him
and I said, "Jean,
you're Jean Gritz?
You commanded the Bay of Pigs?"
And he says to me, "Fucking Kennedy. We
could have won that thing."
And that was the very first time
I ever saw that kind of that flash of
anger.
And I thought, "Oh, I I understand
1963."
Do you think LBJ was involved?
You know, to me that just seems like a
bridge too far. But, the people that I
know who believe that LBJ was involved
do have some compelling
evidence, I guess.
And what do you And what do you say
about the Israelis being involved?
I I've come to believe that the Israelis
were involved. And why? What What would
What would their stake have been in it
in 1963?
>> absolutely livid that John Kennedy not
only would not give them a nuclear
weapon, but would have not allowed them
to develop a nuclear weapon.
But, wouldn't there be enormous risk for
them in taking out an American leader?
Oh, yeah.
Enormous, like incalculable risk. Yes.
And so, why would you do it anyhow?
Because they saw it as a matter of their
own survival. Remember, the whole idea
was that the Arabs were going to push
them into the sea. There wouldn't be one
Jew left.
And so,
>> Oh oh oh, hence from the river to the
sea.
From the Jordan to the Mediterranean.
Yes.
Yeah.
>> Wow.
Wow. I'll add something. There I have a
friend at the White House.
And
we were talking, I'm going to say this
was
This was almost a year ago.
And I said offhandedly, "Thank God the
president released all the remaining
Kennedy documents, cuz now we know all
this stuff about Oswald and James
Angleton that we never knew." And he
said to me, "He didn't really sell of
it." And I said, "Yeah, he did. Kind of
famously so."
He said, "No, he didn't."
And I said, "What's left?" And he said,
"Every document that remains classified
has the word Israel in it."
And I said, "Damn it.
I was hoping they weren't involved."
But but let me ask you this because